[{"answer": "No, no This is all wrong. Where's the Chicken Cashew", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Race.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I didn't order any of this. I'm not paying for this", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Your boyfriend reads the Daily Worker? What is he? A communist", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Race.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Maybe he's just", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "He's back. And I knew he would be someday.  Man that's some tart cider!", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Race.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Hi", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Oh, nothing in particular", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Race.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I did not cheat", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I know it's not the same", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Race.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yeah, we had a good run", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Come on get your bead on. We're going to be late", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Race.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Not my friend, it's my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "On Prancer on Dasher, on my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Race.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "He wants to meet you? I'll tell you what. I'll show up. He doesn't know we're friends. I'll pretend I haven't seen you since High School. I'll back up the story", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Race.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Not bad? It's gorgeous!", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Ho ho ho Well come on little Princess, tell that place what you want. Don't be shy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Race.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "my friend speaks the language of all children. A notchie watchie dotchie do.", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Race.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Hello", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I'm sorry, uh", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Race.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Oh, my friend , my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "But I digress. Let me see, now. You were standing at one end of the line and I was right next to you. And I remember we were even for like, the first five yards and then , BOOM,...You were gone", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Race.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Head start, oh no absolutely not", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I want a racing car set", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Race.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "But I want a racing car set", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I knew that Commie stuff was going to get us in trouble", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Race.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Communism, You didn't realize Communism was a sensitive issue? What do you think has been going on in the world for the past 60 years? Wake up and smell the coffee. K I guess I screwed up", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Now you're going to see what kind of liar you're mixed up with", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Race.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "If he beats me, I'll not only give you a raise, I'll send you to that place for two weeks", "qsentId": 30}]